谨以此片追忆逝去的童年，如果你也有这样的童年的话欢迎加入我们的贴吧"神剑传奇"。本作品之片源来自互联网，版权归原公司所有。任何组织和个人不得公开传播或用于任何商业盈利用途，一切后果由该组织或个人承担！制作者不承担任何法律及连带责任！请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
France 2. Ecipse Animaz ion, Toonean Productions Xll Ing
传司
FR
2.∈
XIl Ins
France 2. Ecipse Animaz ion, Toonean Product ions Xll Ine
翻译：英语辅导频道
输入/时间轴/压制：harry159821/黑月
pt oy
ChRistophe Pujol and Thomas FoRood
校对：
一
Royal guard! No one. moves
卫兵搜查谁都不准动
think that's a safe bet
我想那样应该万无一失
The outlaw, Princess Djana
有人看见逃犯裘娜公主
and her friends have been
seen in the neighbourhood
租她的朋友在这附近露面
You haven't seen them
have you, innkeeper?
你没有见到她们吗店老板
第？集
mean no offence, your Lordship
我无意冒犯您殿下
but with all
the taxes these days
可从这几天的酒菜钱来看
I get, very few customers
我这都没几个顾客光临啊
You are aware of what happens
to anyone who harbours rebels?
你会留意有谁包庇那些逃犯的吧
Oh, yes my Lord, I value my life
噢当然殿下我很珍惜自己生命的
we've searched
everywhere Lord Bragan
们到处都搜了布拉刚殿
There's no"trace of them
没有他的踪影
You're not having anything?
你们不喝点什
Not even a little herbal tea?
要不要来点清凉茶啊
Flaming dragons
燃烧的龙啊
When nt comes
to harbouring
rebe
提到匿藏逃犯
no one can hold
a candle to Silkarl
没人比塞尔更擅长了
Yes, thanks. Silkar
没错谢谢塞尔卡
You were perfect
你刚才表现真不错
though your chimney
could use a good cleaning
不过你的烟囱需要好好清洗一番
一桨某童园即测业
bujueejo poob B esn pIno
Keuulyo inoA y noun
though your chimney
could use a good cleaning
不过你的烟囱需要好好清洗一番了
m famished
What's on the menu?
我饿今天准备了什么吃的啊
What aboutHerik'?▲
Isn't he eating with you?
哈里克呢他不跟你们一起吃吗
His eminence s meditating
他出众的地方就是沉思
想
Worldly things
just don't interest him
尘世的东西他都没有兴趣
Not even my Fangor stew
他对我的炖梵高都没兴趣吗
Go and fetch him, will you:Wip?
威你去把他找来行吗
I knew it! I knew
it was too good to last.
我就知道好事持续不了多长时间
Herik! Herik! Wake up!
哈里克哈里克醒醒
Theyre waiting
for us at the inn!
她们在酒馆等我们呢
They re waiting
r us
们在酒馆等我们呢
威普你要打断我
was just about to pass
throughe the portal of telepathy!
刚要通过传心木之门啊
on anaemia8m留
你要钱你
On anaempty stonach?
你要删进行吗
Come on
let's go have some lunch
来吧我们去吃午餐
. won't need lunch, Wip
on the other side of the portal
还在传心术门外我不需要吃午餐威普
八
Well,my lovelies,
我的宝贝们
what is it that you have
poted that should know about?
你们给我带回什么好消息了啊
Aahh… the young Shogi.
啊是那个小术士
l-won't need anything
我不需要吃什么东西
My spirit will be
free from physical limits
我的灵魂会摆脱肉体的控制
I'll travel great distances
the blink of an, eye
然后一眨眼间穿越长远距离
ButcHerik!
Do it after lunch!
临哈里克用完午餐再说行不行
Silkar has prepared
a real feast and
塞尔卡准备一顿丰盛的大餐
Oh no, he s gune again!
哦他又离开
Morgan. Morgan?
莫刚莫刚
Morgan? Do you hear me?
Answer! It's me, Herik
莫刚听到我说话吗请回答
是我哈里克
What's this
这是什么把戏
It seems the young Shogi
has found the telepathic portal
看样子小术士找到了传心术之门
Very dangerous, little Shogi
真危险啊小术士
separate your body
and mind like that
象那样将你的肉体和灵魂分开
to those with more
skill in such matters!
你更擅长传心术的人面前
Come, my Griffins
过来我的兽兵
Herik? Hey, are you alright?
哈里克嘿你还好吧
Please say something
说话啊
inCome on
题快点尔非准备的美味要凉了
Silkar's stew is getting cold
Now, you shall obey me
现在开始你要服从我的命令
Herik? We're
honoured by your presence
哈里克你来了我们真感到荣幸
Wait for your chance
then take xcalibur
等待机会拿到神剑
and bring it to me
along with the Book of Life
然后把它和生命之书一起带来给我
Taste this. Choice Fangor
尝学这个我的炖梵高
Lost your appetite
没胃口吗
没胃 petite
Lost your appetite?
没胃口吗
guess not
看来不是
Herik
哈里克
Ahhh! A Griffin!
有怪兽
Help! Mama
救命妈妈
O
Mama! MaMa
妈妈妈
Back, beast! Get away!
滚回去怪兽滚
Griffins are more
ferocious than that.
怪兽向来不是很凶残的
He must be il
他肯定是有点不正常
It's all right
my little one
没事了我的小宝贝
Mama is here
妈妈在这
I guess you'll be returning to
you precious studies, eh, Herik?
我想你要回去继续钻研吧哈里克
How about a good siesta first!
先好好午休一下如何
You should at
least get
good rest
在你继续传心术修炼之前
before you go through that
portal where you don't eat
你至少得好好休息下吧
到那时候连吃的都没有
Going somewhere, Herik?
哈里克要去哪
Better get cleaned up firs
不过你最好先整理下自己
You don 't want to
make a bad first impression
你也不想留个不好的第一印象吧
Now! Take the sword
趁现在把神剑拿到手
Herik! No!
哈里克不要
No! You might hurt Herik
不行能会伤到哈里克
e
Hey! Give that back!
把生命之书
He can't go=far
他走不子多远的
心
g
Take care: of Herik
照顾一下哈里克
e
Not quite yourself
today, are you, Herik?
哈里克今天真不象你是不是
What do you want
that Book for. Griffin?
怪兽你拿生命之书做付<
You can't even read
你害都看不
N
What happened, Herik?
哈里克发生什么事了
It's not like you
这可一点不象你
to let one of these
primitive beasts beat you
被这个原始动物打倒了啊
I'll get him
我会抓到他的
get him
多
k
A
Quiet, you miserable donkey
安分点你这头蠢驴
We have them. my lord
我们找到他殿下
The- young Shogi
and the Barbarian!
是小术士和蛮族人
/What about Djana?
还有裘娜呢
Isdon't know.. I see only two
我不清楚只找到两个
Don't lose sight of them
别跟丢他们了
They'I. lead
us to the princes
他会带我们去找芸的
They 'pLead
他倒会带我付去找的
They'll lead
us to the princes
他会带我们去我娜的
Fc
M
Come, ont/ Give us the book
and we will let you
生命之书还来我
八
Hurry, Princess
Before he gets to the Forest
快点公主殿下趁他还没有进去森林
Wait! Stop!
等等站住
What
f?
Are you trying to say something?
你是想说么吗
Don' t believe him, Princess
主殿下不要相信他
g
Sorry! I was sure I'd get him
抱歉我以为击中他了
Timis- Griffin is pretty nimble
这头圣兽身手真敏捷
这头怪兽身手真敏捷
This Griffin is pretty nimble!
来
He's definitely
not like the others
他跟其他怪兽明显不一样
You let him get away
with the Book of Lif
让他拿着生命之书跑了啊
What's the matter with him?
他到底怎么了啊
Come, on before he really
bites off more than he can chew
我们跟上吧不知道他一个人能不能应付
会
今
A
s At
(
N
M
He was exhausted!
He can't be far
他已经筋疲力尽了走不了多远
We have to find him
Wip, do you see anything?
我们得找到他威普发现什么了吗
You're taking
too long! Which way
你速度真慢走哪边啊
Listen, you spoiled brat
听着乳臭未干的小子
our great great
grandfather wasn't, born
我学会喷火的时候
when Ispat, my first flame
你的曾曾曾祖父还没出生呢
change your tune
注意你说话的语气
or you can find your
lousy Book without me
然你自己去找那本破书吧
Easy. Wip
It's bad for your nose
别上火威普对你鼻子不好
It's not, my fault
ost his stupid book
他丢了那本破书又不是我的错
Keep a sharp lookout
给我瞪大眼睛留心了
If we can find Djana
before her friends do
如果能比她朋友先找到她
There he is! Watch out
他在那小心
D
Don' t let me use Xcalibur. Griffin
别逼我用神剑怪兽
Give us the book!
把生命之书还给我们
mps
捣蛋鬼们
Hey? Eole!
嘿风神怎么了
发
Heyl:,, Youmlittle devil
你这个小坏蛋
He's getting away
他跑了
I've never seen Imps
help a Griffin before
我从没见过捣蛋鬼们帮怪兽
Herik!
哈里克
Stay away
滚开
Herik! Stop it!
This is no joke!
哈里克住手这可不是闹着玩的
What's that
This Griffin is your friend?
么这头怪兽是你们的朋友吗
He saved your life?
你是说他救了你吗
H
bad
那个哈里克是坏蛋
Herik! Have you gone crazy
哈里克你是不是疯了
Give me the sword!
把神剑给我
What's got into him
Tara! Tara
塔拉塔拉
lost him
我跟丢了
This one is smarter
' than the average griffin
这只怪兽比其他怪兽聪明多
Where's Herik?
哈里克去哪了
He… he attacked me
他攻击了我
nabbed xcalibur
抢走了神剑
His eyes were
他的眼里
don' t know
like someone possessed
我说不清楚就好象被人制了
you want my opinion
想不想听我的意见
I think all that
telepathy went to his head
他满脑子就是传心术
What telepathy. Wip?
什么传心术威普
ou know… that portal
thing he was searching for
传
n the blink of an
e, blahblah blah
穿越远的距
He did that?
他是在研究那个
I thought you two
were just kidding around
我以为你们两个只是在开玩笑
le did that?
他是在研究那个正
I thought you two
were just kidding a
round
我以为你们两个只是在开玩笑
Oh, he did it
他就是在钻研这个
He said he was going
through the portal, without lunch
他还说不吃牛餐就穿越传心术之门
then he closed his eyes
and shook like a leaf
然后他闭上眼睛身体象落叶一样抖动
Crazy Shogi ideas
疯狂的三基寺想法
We'dbetter talk to morgan
找
Wip. go and find him on
thecisland of the Shogis
威你去三寺岛找他
and -meet us on the beach!
然后到海边跟我碰头
Well, you've made
short work of my dogs,
你解决了我的走狗
but let's see how
you handle their master
不过看看你如何对付他们的主人
He
y!
No, Bragan
住手布拉刚
手布拉刚
It's the Griffin
who . has the Book of Life
那头怪兽拿走了生命之书
This Shogi is with us!
这个小术士是我们的人
Are you sure we
can trust him, Kwodahn?
你确定我们可以信任他吗科沃达
How reassuring
真放心啊
Oh.. Oh man
哦天啊
Am I sorry I ate that stew now!
现在真后悔吃那么多
酒
画
Morgan! Morgan
Morgan! Something
has happened to Herik.
莫刚哈里克出事了
He can't escape us now, my lord
现在他逃不了了殿下
We're here, Morgan!
我们到了莫刚
Meet Diana and Taral
见表娜和塔拉
e
We need your help, Morgan
我们需要你的帮助莫啊
We 'think herik
tried some Shogi technique
哈里克可能在修炼什么三基寺法术
but something went wrong
然后出问题
The telepathic portal, wip told m
传心术之闪威普告诉我
Herik newer should
have thied to master it
哈里克不应该在还学会
禁止其他炱魂进入之前
before learaing to
block out other spirit
就让自己的灵魂脱离体
Someone more
powerfull has taken control
个有装力的人控制了他
Kwodahn? How?
科达吗{么会
What's he (one with Herik?
他对哈里克做了什
Kwodahn transferred
another consciousness into Herik
科沃达把另一个魂魄转移到哈里克体内
and trapped
Herik in another / body
然后把哈里克的灵魂困在其他肉体里
The Griffin!
是那个怪兽
That likes to explain
its, strange behaviour
那就可以解释哈里克奇怿的萼动了
That likes to explain
And the spirit of the Griffin
now inhabits Herik's bod
而怪兽的灵魂现在霸占了哈里克的肉体
I can break this
pell telepathically
我可以用传心术破解这个魔咒
but we must find them both
不过我们必须找到他们两个
You're sure he's in
there with the Book of Life?
你确定他和生命之书都在那里吗
Well, have a look
去看看
And remember Shogi
I'm watching you
不过小术士记着我在看着你
y
That came from the cliffs
是从那边过来的
Wip! Find the Griffin quick
威普赶快去找怪兽
Tell him were
bringing Morgan to hel
诉他莫刚过来帮我们了
That sounds crazy.
but whatever you say
听起来很疯狂不过如你所愿了
If-he's hiding on the cliff
如果他藏身在悬崖
we'd better go by boat
我们最好坐船过去
I'll ride up to the top
那我骑冯去
in case he tries
going back to the forest
以防他逃回森林
Don't worry, Herik
we'll get you out of there!
别担心哈里克我们我们会救你离开的
Just hang on until
Morgan and Djana get here
再坚持一下莫刚和裘娜就快到
No. Herik
住手哈里克
If you destroy your own body
如果你损坏了自已的肉体
you'l never: be
ableLto-reoccupy.
你的灵魂就永远回不去
Concentrate, Herik
集中精神哈里克
Open your consciousness.
打开你的意识
Let me enter
让我进去
Bragan!
是布拉刚
He can't spoil: your
telepathic connection, can he?
他的出现不会扰乱你的传心感应吧
N
Excellent
He has the Book
太棒了他拿到生命书
as in-my hands
命之书一到手
YsesoomEas it's inem
anas
生命之书一至
AS:SoCI t
NN列
hand
As 'soon -as-it's-inmmy hand
命之书一到
we-=no Longer need
de
我们就不要那个小术士了家吗
写
K
Herik! No!
哈里克不要
Now.Herik. now!
现在哈里克就趁现在
Come back!- Now!
回去你的肉体就趁现在
Herik?
哈里克
Herik? Is that really you?
哈里克的是你自己吗
… think so
我想是的
重
t
It'sgalright, he got throug
事了他成功回去了
A
Good wor
得不
Now give me the Book of Life
现在把生命之书交给我
Wait a minute
You might not need those
等下你也许不用出手
As you: wish
如你所愿
but lthought that it was
xcalibur that you really wanted
可我认为神剑才是你真正想要的
'll take what'
canget, when d can/get
能得到的时候我定不会放过
Hand it over
交给我
Let,me get Xcalibur for you
让我去把神剑拿来给你吧
know how to
win Diana's confidence
我知道怎么赢得裘娜的信任
She's in love with me
她爱上我了
a bit conceited isn' t he?
他可真有点自负不是吗
All right. But make it quick
那好过动作快点
Hold on, What about the Book?
站那生命之书怎么
Djana may be suspicious
if she sees don't have it
要是裘娜看到我没有生命之书
可能会起疑的
Don't you worry
you'll soon have them both
别担心你很快会都得到他们的
You have until-nightfall
我给你日落之前的时间
be waitin
at the Royal Palac
我会在王宫等着
Herik? Are you all right?
哈里克你还好吧
Ive got a terrible headache
and my shoulder is killing me
很痛肩膀也酸得要命
Ive got a terrible headache
Ir've got a terrible headache
and my shoulder is killing me,
头很痛肩膀也酸得要命
but my own body
never felt so good
不过我全身从来没有感觉这么舒
Oh. Herik
哦哈里克
thought you left us forever.
我以为你远开我
He - nearly did
他差点就回环来
leeneeag nitid
He nearly did
他差点就回区来
Heeneeapyditi
Herik's mental powers
are-already-quite=impressive
如果刚才发生了什么意外
f somewhat undisciplined
哈里克的灵魂就回不来了
Not many can; pass throug
the portal on th
没几个人可以第次就穿战传
know sit was reckless
to try on my own, Morga
我知道自有点卤莽了莫
and I never would have
made it back withou
没有你的帮助我永远都
You saved me from a
life as a hideous bea
你让我摆脱那种丑动物的生活
u think
你觉得何塔
What-dol you think Tara?
你觉得如何塔拉
Should I ask Morgan to help. me
jump into a betterelocking body?
我是不是应该叫莫刚帮忙
的身体啊
Wips you' re pertect
justs the wa
are
成普你水来的样子就是最好的
m∈a阳
真的吗你说真的吗
Really? You mean it?
真的吗你说的吗
lOwado you believe me?
现在你总该相信了吧
who-wounldr want to
be -any thing but a dragon?
咖
uobenp B inq6uAue⊙q
ol QUEM pINon OLM
Cuobenp e ing DumyRAuB ag
Who would want to
be-anything but a dragon?
做龙多好啊
Y
Still waiting, Bragan?
还在等啊布拉刚
Are you really so stupid
你真的那么笨
that you expect Herik
to bring you Xcalibur
期待哈里克把神剑给你送来吗
But… why not
可是为什么不
You told me yourself
at I could trust him!
你自己跟我说可以信任他的啊
That Herik wasn't himself
当时那个哈里克不是他本
What are you talking about?
你到底在说什
I-don't really expect you
to tell the difference yourself.
我真不期待你自己能说出不同在哪里
Myself? Himself? What
我自己他自己到底是什么
scIPT SuPeKTISOK
SCRIPT SUPERYISOR
5cH#果
ExecuTIYE STORY EDITOR
CRIPT CONSULTANT
SCHiNe是
erectLY
EDITOR
B匙
Eecu o SomE eDITOR
erEcuTTYE STORY EDIToR
TORT
RTISTS
5W3B5
'Cube OwSNeTulTT
STUDIO RARA
TOHIINRO EITISTS
STUDIO MA
相Ⅲ多
d HYNooA. xoi YuIstMIYOY Notongowd
asama. BYNYw omanIs
sTuDonreite miot se
RO DUCTION IDMINSTRXTOR- TOONCTH PRODUCTIONS TIl INC.
PDvo"从x相xqe
是J
PRODUCTIONS Il
TILLOT
PRODUCTION3DMm是 PT PRODUCTiON I眠
3D. MODELIN∈
3D-MODELING
GRIBOVILLE
GRIBOUILLE
OTOHRXPMY
sTerne
∈TR
PuTO eTrO
DirecI
sD-MOD LNG wuPEXTtORS
OuCTON SECRETIRY
DIrEC
器留照
e9103 (0/cots ror
3D.NO
REcToR
o4 Toe
L器1
SuPEKTISOKS
DD吐N
DeVeLop∈R
IXTIST3
C6 ARTISTS 30MODEt
Cs IRTI
CE AKTIST
eon
A
MOTION CAPTURE
STUICON STUDIO
翻译：英语辅导频道
输入/时间轴/压制：harry159821/黑月
校对：